life is uncertain and unpredictable
one moment you are basking in the Sun
the next moment you're facing a storm
thankfully with the right term plan you
can stay assured that whether days are
good or bad you and your loved ones are
financially protected for the future
presenting ICICI Pro iprotect Smart a
term plan that provides Financial
Protection to you and your family up to
99 years of age and offers you the
flexibility to choose the plan option
that suits your need
this plan provides enhanced protection
with life cover terminal illness
critical illness and permanent
disability let's understand this in
detail with iprotect smart you can
choose your level of protection
first is life option the life cover is
paid to the nominee on the occurrence of
death of the life assured or diagnosis
of terminal illness
and in the case of permanent disability
due to an accident the future premiums
under the policy are waived off
the second is the life plus option
in this option along with the benefits
under the life option the life assured
is also covered for accidental death
benefit in case of death due to an
accident within the accidental death
benefit term the nominee gets the
accidental death benefit as a lump sum
over and above the life cover
the third is life and health option
in this option along with the benefits
under the life option
the life assured is also covered for the
accelerated critical illness benefit
a coverage against 34 critical illnesses
on diagnosis of covered critical
illnesses the plan will pay the life
assured a lump sum to meet their
financial needs and the fourth and final
option is the all-in-one option
in this option along with the benefits
under the life option the life for sure
discovered for both accidental death
benefit and accelerated critical illness
benefit
this plan gives you the flexibility to
pay the premium once
for a limited period
or throughout the policy term what's
more
this plan will provide you with tax
benefits on premiums paid
ICICI Pro iprotect Smart allows you to
take the life cover in a way that meets
your financial requirement the life
cover can be paid to your beneficiary as
following options first lump sum benefit
where the entire benefit amount is
payable as a lump sum second income
benefit where 10 percent of the benefit
amount is payable to the beneficiary
every year for 10 years third lump sum
and income benefit where the percentage
of the summer short to be paid out as a
lump sum is selected at the start and
the balance summer short is paid out in
equal monthly installments in advance
for over 10 years and the fourth and
final option increasing income benefit
where the benefit amount is payable in
monthly installments for 10 years
starting with 10 percent of the benefit
amount per annum in the first year the
income amount will increase by 10
percent per annum with simple interest
now let's see how this plan works
Ria is a 32 year old working
professional she is aware of a loan to
buy a house realizing the need for
protection in her fast-paced life Riya
invests 18 037 rupees per annum in ICICI
Pro I protect smart with a base life
cover of one crore rupees and a critical
illness benefit of 25 lakh rupees for 30
years
now at age 40 Ria is diagnosed with a
critical illness at this point she
receives 25 lakh rupees as a lump sum
the policy continues with the reduced
summer short of 75 lakh rupees
the premium proportionally gets reduced
to
8959 rupees per annum now in case of
Ria's unfortunate demise her nominee
gets a lump sum death benefit of 75 lakh
rupees and the policy terminates
what are you waiting for secure your
future with the ICICI Pro iprotect smart
plan today
thank you
foreign
[Music]